Guide to the Kermit Carlyle Parsons papers, circa 1945-1999
Parsons, Kermit Carlyle papers, circa 1945-1999
- Series III. Research and Consulting
  - Clarence Stein research files
    - Clarence S. Stein - Community Architect: Selected Letters, Sketches, and Unpublished Writings, Clarence Stein Chronology and List of Archictural, Planning, and Housing Projects, April 1997 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Community Architect: Selected Letters, Sketches, and Unpublished Writings, Bibliography: Articles and Books by Clarence S.Stein, Bibliography: Articles and Books About Clarence Stein and his Work, April 1997 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Community Architect: Selected Letters, Sketches, and Unpublished Writings, Biographical Sketches, People associated with Stein and his projects, April 1997 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Dedication of Olive Tjaden Hall with Dean Seeley, Olive Tjaden and President Rhodes, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - "The Morris House", 1950 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - "Comparative Social Planning Bibliography" prepared by Cary Hershey, August 1973 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Copies of Stein plans (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Extra copies of 1932 letters, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Notes on 1931-1932 correspondence (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Extra copies of 1935 letters, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - FN/Stein Letters, 1941-1944 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Stein correspondence, February 14, 1946 - December 21, 1949 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - FN/Stein Letters, 1931 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - FN/Stein Letters, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Copy of 1933 footnote corrections and selections, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Extra copies of 1931-1932 letters (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - FN/Stein Letters, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - FN/Stein Letters, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Copy of 1934 footnotes (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - FN/Stein Letters, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - FN/Stein Letters, 1936-1940 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Manuscript drafts and copies of Stein correspondence, August 1986 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Copy of 1932 footnote corrections and deletions (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Copies of archival material from the Stein papers (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Typescripts of letters from the Stein papers (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - "Form, Space and the Ornament in the Large Scale Housing Projects of Clarence S. Stein, 1929-1941" by Anne Boyer Cotten (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - Aline Stein bequest, early discussions, 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - Committee on Clarence Stein Center for New Towns, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - Stein Center/Fellowships committee, Stein endowment, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - Stein committee, February 1994 (Box 48, Folder 27)
    - Clarence Stein fellowships, 1994-1995 (Box 48, Folder 28)
    - Clarence Stein fellowship applicants, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 29)
    - Clarence Stein fellowships committee correspondence, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 30)
    - Clarence Stein fellowships correspondence to John Simon, 1994-1995 (Box 48, Folder 31)
    - Aline Stein bequest, early correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 32)
    - Dean McMinn (Box 48, Folder 33)
    - Clarence Stein fellowships, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 34)
    - Aline MacMahon Stein correspondence regarding Stein Center and bequest (Box 48, Folder 35)
    - Clarence Stein Center committee, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 36)
    - "The Friendly Interchange: A Planning Study of Interstate 95 and the Huntington Avenue Expressway as They Affect a Community in Cranston, Rhode Island", Blair Associates, October 19, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 37)
    - Olive Tjaden estate (Box 48, Folder 38)
    - Olive Tjaden Hall exhibit (Box 48, Folder 39)
    - City and Regional Planning Program chronology; Gilmore Clarke correspondence (Box 48, Folder 40)
    - Cornell Plantations, 1996-1997 (Box 48, Folder 41)
    - Eugenie Birch (Box 48, Folder 42)
    - Larry Anderson - MacKaye biographer (Box 48, Folder 43)
    - Review of 'Cities in Our Future' (Box 48, Folder 44)
    - Referee of article on Lewis Mumford and Portland, Oregon (Box 48, Folder 45)
    - Review of Frank Lloyd Wright article for Journal of the American Planning Association, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 46)
    - CSS Letters - new introduction, drafts, January 1996 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Aline Stein support for editing of CS Stein Letters, 1987-1990 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Stein Center - bequest/proposals/correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Stein bequest, CIW/Goldsmith, 1985-1986 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Gerhard Fehl correspondence, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - The Cornell Campus review, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Society for American City and Regional Planning History, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Phased retirement (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Stein article on Cambridge University (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Lakewood High School, Class of 1945 50th Reunion (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - SACRPH meeting, November 1991 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Center for Advanced Study in the Visual Arts, October 1993 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Permissions for Stein material in thesis on Walter Arensberg, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Gordon Stephenson correspondence (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Julian Whittlesey correspondence, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Neighborhood research, San Juan, Puerto Rico - Alan Feldt (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - "Clarence Stein's Middle Years: The Transition form Greenbelt Consultant to Urban Policy Statesman", 1993 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Spann - RPAA book review (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - William Jenkins' research on Ernest Bohn, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Johns Hopkins Press agreement, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Graham Foundation grant proposal, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - John Gallery correspondence (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - CSS Letters financial support, request to McMinn (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Stein Endowment Fund (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - CSS and New York State and City housing reform (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - CSS, ethical culture and Workingmans School, The Hudson Guild (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - CSS early years, incomplete manuscript, October 2000 (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - CSS early years, notes (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - Stein biography research notes, ethical/culture/social (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - "Growing Up in New York and Paris: Clarence Stein's Urban Roots and Values", 1999 (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - CSS Growing Up, drafts and notes (Box 49, Folder 31)
    - Stein Letters introduction (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - Books used in CSS early years (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - Copies of Stein Letters manuscript (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - Copies of Stein Letters manuscript (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - Copies of Stein Letters manuscript (Box 49, Folder 36)
    - Copies of Stein Letters manuscript (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - 1903-1909 Stein Letters, edited by Jerry (Box 49, Folder 38)
    - 1910-1919 Stein Letters, edited by Jerry (Box 49, Folder 39)
    - Early years, notes and drafts (Box 49, Folder 40)
    - 1903-1918 originals (Box 49, Folder 41)
    - Stein archive index (Box 49, Folder 42)
    - CSS-Mumford (Box 49, Folder 43)
    - Research on Stanford planning and Stein at Stanford University, January 1988 (Box 49, Folder 44)
    - address book (Box 49, Folder 45)
    - Japanese note paper (Box 49, Folder 46)
    - Radburn Association correspondence, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 47)
    - "Clarence Stein and the Greenbelt Towns" drafts, 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 48)
    - Sunnyside Homes (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - "The Stevenage Town Center: The Influence of Clarence S. Stein on its Design", student paper, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Sunnyside Gardens (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Radburn, New Jersey article (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Research notes - Housing Act of 1934, Eccles (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Housing Act of 1934, House hearings (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - CSS articles/reports (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - CSS letters, biographical sketches, February 1994 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - General CSS articles, 1944-1953 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - CSS articles (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - "Clarence Stein's Middle Years: The Transition from Greenbelt Consultant to Urban Policy Statesman" by Kermit C. Parsons (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - CSS letters, biographical sketches (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - CSS letters, biographical sketches-drafts (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Stein letters' introduction draft (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Stein research bibliography and sources (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Stein bibliographies (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Benton MacKaye and the Appalachian Trail conference, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Appalachian Trail and the RPAA paper, September 1996 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Appalachian Trail/Benton MacKaye and the RPAA-early drafts, notes (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Woodrow Wilson Center research proposal, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Stein manuscript, summer 1990 edition, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Stein manuscript, summer 1990 edition, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Stein manuscript (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Stein manuscript (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Stein manuscript introduction drafts, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - "New Towns: Extinct or Evolving?" conference notes (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Clarence Stein correspondence, 1950s (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - Stein manuscript - footnote repair, September 1990 (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Stein manuscript corrections (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - Stein correspondence January 1954-December 1959, final format editing, August 1989 (Box 50, Folder 30)
    - Stein correspondence January 1960-Fall 1968, final format changes, May 1989 (Box 50, Folder 31)
    - Stein Letters 1910-1930, final draft, September 1990 (Box 50, Folder 32)
    - Stein Letters 1930s, final draft, September 1990 (Box 50, Folder 33)
    - Stein manuscript, 1988 edition, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 34)
    - Stein manuscript introduction, 2nd draft, May 1990 (Box 50, Folder 35)
    - Stein manuscript, new introduction, April 1990 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - CSS correspondence and unpublished essays, 1916-1926 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - CSS correspondence, circa 1931 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Stein Letters draft (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Stein Letters draft (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - "Clarence Stein and the Greenbelt Towns" final copy, August 1988 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Stein Letters (second half) draft, undated (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Stein Letters (second half) draft, undated (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - "Early Letters: 1905-1911" first draft (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Drafts of "Home Again" and "The Twenties" (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Stein manuscript introduction draft, May 1989 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Stein manuscript draft: "Introduction" through "Kitimat, B.C.", November 1990 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Introduction notes, August 11, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - "Editorial Policy: The Papers of Clarence Stein" draft, November 1993 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - "The Thirties: Success and Stress - 1931-1939" draft, May 1989 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Stein manuscript draft: "Introduction" through "Kitimat, B.C.", June 26, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Greenbelt correspondence and draft (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous draft pages and notes (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Stein Letters draft, part 2, December 14, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Stein Letters draft, part 2, December 14, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Writings of C.S. Stein - Editorial Policy (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Joondallup Regional Centre - A Plan for a Metropolitan Regional Centre in Western Australia "given to Aline Stein by Gordon Stephenson (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - C.S. Stein Book Proposal - Scully Grant (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - RPAA/Stein - Virginia Regional Planning Conference, July 1931 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - National Endowment for the Arts - Individual Research Grant Proposal, July 1994 (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - C.S. Stein Book Bills, National Endowment for the Arts Grants, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - "Shaping the Regional City: 1950-1990" by Parsons, October 1989 (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - "Rus in Urb: A Prologue to the Evaluation of the Impact of the Radburn Idea on Modern Town Planning" by Parsons (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - "Papers Toward a Biography of Clarence S. Stein" by Parsons, May 1993 (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous articles and notes on Clarence Stein (Box 51, Folder 30)
    - "Collaborative Genious: The Regional Planning Association of America" by Parsons, Autumn 1994 (Box 51, Folder 31)
    - "Clarence Stein and the Greenbelt Towns: Settling for Less" by Parsons, Spring 1990 (Box 51, Folder 32)
    - "Clarence Stein's Middle Years: The Transition from Greenbelt Consultant to Urban Policy Statesman" by Parsons, November 13, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 33)
    - "British and American Community Design: Clarence Stein's Manhattan Transfer. 1924-1974" by Parsons, July 7, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 34)
    - "American Influence on Stockholm Post World War II Suburban Expansion" by Parsons (Box 51, Folder 35)
    - Architectural Forum, April 3, 1953 (Box 51, Folder 36)
    - RPA and Regional Planning Documents (Box 51, Folder 37)
    - "The Regional Planning Ideas of the RPAA, 1925 - 1965," Presented to Society for American City and Regional Planning History, October 1995 (Box 51, Folder 38)
    - "The Regional Planning Ideas of the RPAA, 1925 - 1965," Presented to Society for American City and Regional Planning History, October 1,995 (Box 51, Folder 39)
    - "The Regional Planning Ideas of the RPAA, 1925 - 1965," Presented to Society for American City and Regional Planning History, October 1,995 (Box 51, Folder 40)
    - "The Regional Planning Ideas of the RPAA, 1925 - 1965," Presented to Society for American City and Regional Planning History, October 1,995 (Box 51, Folder 41)
    - "The Regional Planning Ideas of the RPAA, 1925 - 1965," Presented to Society for American City and Regional Planning History, October 1,995 (Box 51, Folder 42)
    - "The Regional Planning Ideas of the RPAA, 1925 - 1965," Presented to Society for American City and Regional Planning History, October 1,995 (Box 51, Folder 43)
    - The Regional Planning Ideas of the RPAA - Drafts, July-September 1995 (Box 51, Folder 44)
    - Journal of the American Planning Association, Birch Correspondence, January 1993 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - RPAA, Stein Articles (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Community Architect: Selected Letters, Sketches, and Unpublished Papers, by Parsons, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Community Architect: Selected Letters, Sketches, and Unpublished Papers, by Parsons, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Community Architect: Selected Letters, Sketches, and Unpublished Papers, by Parsons, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - CSS Letters, volume 1, May 1989 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - CSS Letters, volume 2, May 1989 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - CSS Letters, volume 1, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Typescripts of Stein letters; photocopies of Stein collection material (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Typescripts of Stein letters; photocopies of Stein collection material (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Typescripts of Stein letters; photocopies of Stein collection material (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - CSS Letters manuscript drafts [incomplete] (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - CSS Letters manuscript drafts [incomplete] (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - CSS Letters introduction, 3rd draft, July 1990 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Kitimat, British Columbia Photos (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Kitimat, British Columbia Correspondence and Brochures, October 1997 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Kitimat, British Columbia Correspondence and Brochures, October 1,997 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - "Kitimat: A new City" by Stein (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - "District of Kitimat, Official Community Plan" (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Illustrations, Sketches, and Photographs for Clarence S. Stein Manuscript (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Illustrations, Sketches, and Photographs for Clarence S. Stein Manuscript (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Illustrations, Sketches, and Photographs for Clarence S. Stein Manuscript (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Illustrations, Sketches, and Photographs for Clarence S. Stein Manuscript (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - "Financing Affordable Housing: Lessons from Alexander Bing's Innovations at Sunnyside and Radburn in the 1920s" Final Paper (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Urban Development Articles (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Clarence S. Stein Letters (Chapters 12, 13, 14) (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Clarence S. Stein Illustrations - Stockholm, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Clarence S. Stein 1932 Correspondence (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - RPAA Illustrations - Journal of the American Planning Association Articles, May 1994 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Clarence S. Stein Letters and Illustrations, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Clarence S. Stein Radburn Illustrations (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Clarence S. Stein British Town Planning Illustrations (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Community Demographic and Economic Information prepared by the District of Kitimat (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Clarence S. Stein Illustrations - 1920s (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Clarence S. Stein Middle Years - Black and White Illustrations, Photographs (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Clarence S. Stein - New York City Plans, Maps, and Articles (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Phipps Garden Apartments, Queens, 1931 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Housing Policy in New York State, 1919-1926 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Housing Policy in New York State, 1919-1926 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Regional Planning Ideas of the RPAA Draft, 1925-1965 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - "Financing Affordable Housing: Lessons from Alexander Bing's Innovation at Sunnyside and Radburn in the 1920s" by Parsons, November 6, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Journal of the American Planning Association - Greenbelt Towns (1935), 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Journal of the American Planning Association - Greenbelt Towns (1935), 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, Correspondence, and Conferences Regarding Stein (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - "Clarence Stein and the Greenbelt Towns: Settling for Less" by Parsons, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - "Rus in Urb: A Prologue to the Evaluation of the Impact of the Radburn Idea on Modern Town Planning" by Parsons, June 1992 (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Articles about Stein and the RPAA (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous Notes Regarding Stein (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Notes on Stein Page Proofs (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - Map of Greenbelt, MD (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Radburn Town Center, 1929 (Box 53, Folder 32)
    - Clarence S. Stein - 1920s Architecture, Housing & Regional Planning Agenda (Box 53, Folder 33)
    - Aline MacMahon Films (Box 53, Folder 34)
    - Aline MacMahon Oral History and Pictures (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - Sample Pages: "The Writings of Clarence S. Stein" (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - Clarence S. Stein Papers - Editorial Policy, December 1993 (Box 53, Folder 37)
    - Clarence S. Stein Letters - Frontispiece and End Papers (Box 53, Folder 38)
    - Clarence S. Stein Letters - Marketing and Questionnaires, March 9, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 39)
    - Clarence S. Stein Writings - Emails, McCarthy (Box 53, Folder 40)
    - John Hopkins, University Press - Production, Marketing, October 1997 (Box 53, Folder 41)
    - Urban America: Documenting the Planners, 1985 (Box 53, Folder 42)
    - Architectural Forum, July-August 1971 (Box 53, Folder 43)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Biographical and Travel Articles (Box 53, Folder 44)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Sunnyside Deed Restrictions (Box 53, Folder 45)
    - "The Regional Planning Ideas of the Regional Planning Association of America: 1925-1965" by Parsons (Box 53, Folder 46)
    - "Papers Toward a Biography of Clarence S. Stein" Draft by Parsons (Box 53, Folder 47)
    - "Papers Toward a Biography of Clarence S. Stein" Draft by Parsons (Box 53, Folder 48)
    - Clarence S. Stein Writings - Late Drafts, Introductions, Captions, Section Heads, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - "Clarence Stein's Middle Years: The Transition from Greenbelt Consultant to Urban Statesman" by Parsons (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence with Vale, January 5, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - "Papers Toward a Biography of Clarence S. Stein" Draft by Parsons, December 1994 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - "Benton MacKaye - Regional Planner" by Robert McCullough, December 13, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Captions, Maps, and Images for Clarence S. Stein Book (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Candidate Illustrations for Clarence S. Stein Letters Book, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Clarence S. Stein - New York Housing (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Affordable Housing - Santa Fe and Howard County, Colorado (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Affordable Housing Articles (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Affordable Housing, HUD Articles - National Archives (Walker Writing) (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Financing Affordable Housing Articles (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Housing Commission, Regional Planning (1926), New York Archives Invoice (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - RPAA and Regional Planning - Manuscript and Archive Services, August 1995 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Affordable Housing: 1939 Housing Act (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Greenbelt Towns (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Marriner S. Eccles Research, Housing Act of 1934 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Affordable Housing Drafts and Pictures, September 1994 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Los Angeles Housing (1941); Pittsburgh Letters to Associates (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Stein in Los Angeles and Pittsburgh (1938-1942), November 1993 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Indian Head Project (1940-1941), May 20, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Clarence S. Stein in Los Angeles and Pittsburgh (1938-1942), March 1993-November 1993 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Clarence S. Stein's Middle Years; Transitions in Los Angeles and Pittsburgh (Society for American City and Regional Planning History), 1993 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Society for American City and Regional Planning History Meeting in Chicago, December 1993 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Clarence S. Stein - British Transfer, Radburn. "Planning Perspectives" Publications (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Manhattan and Baltimore Transfer Articles (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - "British and American Community Design - Clarence Stein's Manhattan Transfer: 1924-1974" prepared by Parsons, July 7, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Columbia, MD Land Use Plan (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - Clarence S. Stein - British Newtowns (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Clarence S. Stein - British Radburn Transfers, "Planning Perspectives Publication" (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Clarence S. Stein - British Town Planning Notes (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - Clarence S. Stein - British Manuscripts, June 28, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - Oxford and AESOP Materials and Maps, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 33)
    - Associates of Collegiate Schools of Planning Meeting (Pasadena, CA); Paper on C.S. Stein Housing Reform (Box 54, Folder 34)
    - The Journal of the American Institute of Planners, May 1972 (Box 54, Folder 35)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Housing Reform Contribution to New York City (1919-1924) (Box 54, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous Papers by Clarence S. Stein (Box 54, Folder 37)
    - Miscellaneous Stein Correspondence and Sweden Notes (Box 54, Folder 38)
    - Clarence S. Stein Stockholm Notes (Box 54, Folder 39)
    - "Rus in Urb: A prologue to the Evaluation of the Impact of the Radburn Idea on Modern Town Planning" by Parsons, June 6, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 40)